Giant lizards!
Komodo dragons.
Take her to the other side of the river.
O-Okay.
I'll get the BIMs.
You'll what?
That's crazy, Sakamoto!
Hey, hang in there.
Sakamoto, get back here!
What are you doing?!
It isn't exploding!
Wh-Why?
The switch...
isn't working!
I took these BIMs from that kid.
Maybe they...
don't count as my BIMs because I didn't kill him or something?
Sakamoto!
Mr. Taira!
Which ones are mine?
N-Not these, either.
Damn it!
Stay back, damn it!
Lay off us!
M-Mr. Taira!
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is where tomorrow brings a new game
It's time to learn that pain is gain
Ready fight
To squash my past despair
kako no shitsubou nuritsubusu tame ni
I've had to sacrifice my future
gisei ni shite kita mirai
Until my life expires
boku no life ga tsukiru made
I'll keep fighting my fate
sono sadame buchikowashiteiku no sa
Ah, break out and start a revolution
Searching for the exact answer
hitotsu no kotae wo sagashite
I challenge myself to an extreme race
genkai no race ni idonde
I know it's my only chance
ichidokiri no chansu to shitte
I'll overcome my preordained fate
seotta unmei koeteikun da yo
All the way from the farthest ends of the world
saihate no story idaite
I have been wandering without a destination
ate mo naku samayoitsuzuketa
Now a new world emerges from the haze
nijinda new world
The game has only just begun
the game has only just begun
The beginning of the end is in my eyes
ima hajimari no eyes
This is a disaster.
My right leg again...
I'm sorry. You're having to carry everything.
It's fine.
We fit everything in one trunk.
And you have it worse.
No, you do.
We need to stop the bleeding on that leg.
We don't have time.
More importantly, be sure you
keep that girl on your back.
Right.
They're following us.
But y'know, Sakamato...
It's rare to find a guy as good as you these days.
I'm really nothing special.
Why didn't you run and leave us behind?
From your perspective,
we're just an old guy and an unconscious girl you don't even know, slowing you down.
In that situation, no one would blame you if you'd left us to die.
Mr. Taira... Why are you always saying things like that?
Are you... testing me?
I wonder...
I don't know.
But I'm scared.
When you left to go fight,
I wondered if maybe you wouldn't come back.
If you had abandoned me...
It was all I could think about.
I couldn't help it. I was seriously terrified.
What we talked about afterwards...
When that girl said someone wanted to get rid of us...
I can't help but think that maybe she's right.
I was kind to my family,
but I was a monster at work.
I took advantage of loopholes and gray areas in the law.
It wouldn't surprise me if any of them hated me.
This is karma.
Anything you do wrong will come
back to get you in the end.
Yes. This is my punishment.
I...
I... won't betray you.
Th-They're close!
Run! Run for it!
Hey... Wait!
Taira!
Damn it.
Mr. Taira...
Mr. Taira!
Where did you go, Mr. Taira?
We got separated?
No, that isn't right.
If I can't detect him using radar, that means he isn't moving.
Why wouldn't he move at a time like this?
In a situation like this, no one would
blame you if you'd left us to die.
He has all the food and her BIMs.
Maybe he... left her with me,
while he made off with our supplies!
Have I been abandoned?
No way...
I can't believe it.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Screw you, you old bastard!
C-Crap!
Dammit...
That BIM...
Sakamoto!
Are you okay?
I've been looking everywhere for you!
He didn't run away?
We were both looking for each other.
Our radars just canceled each other out?
Mr. Taira, I... I doubted you.
I...
When you're scared, all you can think of is the worst.
I'm no different.
So never give up hope!
Right?
Night of Sacrifice
Right...
But are you sure about this, Mr. Taira?
Weren't you intending to keep your BIM type secret?
Sorry.
I still didn't trust you.
I didn't want to make enemies or let anyone get close.
That's how I've lived.
But you risked your life for me.
You believed in me.
I was so happy.
"If I stay with this person, I'll be saved. So I have to trust him completely."
That's all it was.
The sea breeze!
We're close to the sea.
Mr. Taira...
Look.
Sakamoto!
Hurry!
We've gotta climb this thing?
But what about her?
We'll have to get her up there together.
Let's go!
Right, that's it...
You can do it.
You can do it!
I'll buy you time.
You get up there with the girl.
I can't do it alone.
That ladder's all rusted.
And his BIMs are a homing type.
They'll lock on...
then home in.
But they aren't powerful at all.
Hey!
Climb up there on your own!
Please...
I'm begging you!
Wake up!
Karma...
Is this my punishment?
If we sacrifice her, we can survive.
But...
I can't do something so cruel.
You want me...
You want me to become a monster?
No!
This won't hold them off!
Sakamoto, are you up there yet?
Wh-What are you doing?
Is he insane?
Don't tell me he's gonna sacrifice her so he alone can survive?!
I've lost faith in you.
I've lost faith in you, Sakamoto!
What's that smoke?
Get back, Mr. Taira.
It's one of the corrosive gas type BIMs she has.
It's very hazardous.
Her BIMs?
Back there, you said you could only use your own.
Yes, but I just had an idea.
I found another way.
I made her push the switch.
Didn't know you could do that.
But the gas is spreading.
There's nowhere to run.
It'll be fine...
as long as we're here.
Here, where the sea breeze is blowing.
The sea breeze?
The sea breeze blows in here,
and we're surrounded by rocks.
Places like this are where the
corrosive gas type are most effective.
A-Amazing!
That's amazing, Sakamoto!
This game is different from BTOOOM!.
In BTOOOM!, there isn't any wind,
and you can't take and use someone else's BIMs.
This is the real life BTOOOM!.
Seems a BIM killed someone here.
It isn't recent.
There might have been a game like this before we arrived.
Tired...
Mr. Taira, are you okay?
Well, if we've come this far, we should be safe.
You know, when you climbed up that ladder alone,
I started to wonder what you were thinking.
M-Maybe it's because I can finally relax...
but I feel really dizzy.
Oh, no.
O-Ow! Ouch!
The leg that was bitten just started hurting.
He has a really bad fever!
Are the lizards gone?
Five of them are dead.
I'd bet the rest returned to the forest.
And it still smells like poison around here.
I doubt they'll be back.
Hey. What do you think you're looking at?
Nothing.
I wasn't looking.
Come to think of it,
you didn't do anything weird
while I was out, did you?
Weird?
S-Scum!
You pervert!
W-Wait...
I didn't do anything!
Shut up.
It's written all over your face!
Stay away from me, asshole.
Don't jump to conclusions!
Don't...
Don't touch me!
S-Sorry.
Mr. Taira, are you okay?
Keep going!
Don't just stand there!
Help me out here!
We need to disinfect it.
Help me hold him down.
What are you doing?
Hurry!
No!
I don't want to touch a man!
What are you talking about?
This isn't the time for that!
He got bitten trying to protect you.
Come on!
Okay, here we go!
What'll happen... to us...
from now on?
Hey, there!
Good morning.
Thanks for the all-nighter!
Here, some snacks.
Thank you.
Well?
Anything neat happen?
Nothing notable at the moment.
Oh, my...
Looks like Sakamoto is still alive.
Yes.
He's already made contact with four other players,
but he only killed the first one.
It appears he's gathering allies.
I see.
That sounds like him.
He'll give us some good data.
Make sure you collect it all.
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Our First Cosplay
You won't get cell reception out here.
Wh-What are you doing?
Don't scare me like that.
I was just thinking that we're working together,
but I don't know your name yet.
Was that picture taken in a photo booth?
So you cosplay.
Is that character...
Don't look at my cell phone!
You sicko.
Wh-What are you doing?!
That's my line, you ass.
And I'm not "working with you two".
I don't trust men, so there's no point telling you my name!
Whether you're working with us or not,
I want to ask you this:
All those BIMs and that food you have...
how did you get them?
You didn't just have the trunk, you had crackers and timers,
and corrosive gas types, as well.
You can only use your own BIMs.
To use another player's BIMs, you can't just steal them.
You have to kill the enemy player before they'll belong to you.
How many have you killed?
Sakamoto, are you saying she's a murderer?
Yes.
We need to know what she's thinking,
or she could turn on us at any moment.
Why do I have to tell you that?
It was to protect myself!
I had no choice!
I'd have been...
Is she saying it was self-defense?
Or could this all be an act?
It might be a bit harsh, but you're
under a lot of suspicion right now.
Unless you answer me, I can't take my guard down around you.
All it takes is one hit from behind, and it's over.
If you were to kill us...
you could get the eight chips
you need to escape this island.
I would never...
Sonar!
Is someone here?
Don't move.
It's still far away.
No one was seen, right?
Th-They found me.
I-I'll...
I'll leave this place.
W-Wait.
But if I stay, that guy's gonna come here, right?
The killing will start again.
You should hide, too.
S-Sakamoto...
Wait.
They only found one person.
I'll act as a decoy and draw them off.
When I get back, we'll settle this.
I hold my breath and close my eyes
iki wo sezu me wo fuseta
The sky is glittering so brightly
hikyou na hodo kirameku aozora ga
Coloring the space over our heads
kono machi no zujou wo color
I can't stop shedding tears
tomedonaku namida furaseru kara
I can't just push it aside as memories
omoide ni wa dekinai
Just seeing you made me so happy
au dake de ureshikatta
I didn't understand you
kimi no koto shirazu ni
And hurt you
kizutsukete
Nobody knows
nobody knows
You don't have to give me another chance
gomen ne watashi wo mou
Just forget about me
yurusanaide wasurete
Geez, what the hell am I doing?
When I played the game online,
I used to enjoy helping others like this.
But this time, I'm risking my life.
Time to get rid of them.
I'll run to the other side, and I should appear to be getting farther away.
If they're farther away in my next scan, we won't have to fight.
I head into enemy territory to
recover a kidnapped girl.
Is there a reason to risk my life?
I saw it.
That girl...
she's my...
Episode
Virtual Bride